#### Contact

henriqueph@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/henriqueph (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Java
JavaScript
SPED Fiscal/Contribuições

# Paulo Corrêa

Java / VBA / MySQL / C# Programmer at PHMR Informática Uberlândia

#### Summary

Computer analyst and programmer, passionate about technology. Took part in many projetcs using C#, Java, VBA, JS, Oracle, MySQL, SQL Server, and others. I have worked in many Fiscal and Finantial Projects, such as 'SPED Fiscal', 'Sped Contribuições', 'NFe', 'CTe', and others.

## Experience

PHMR Informática Java / VBA / MySQL / C# Programmer April 2016 - Present (4 years 5 months) Uberlândia, Minas Gerais, Brazil

Responsible for analysis and development of applications using Java, MySQL and VBA.

Avon Cosméticos Finantial / IT Business Analyst October 2008 - March 2016 (7 years 6 months) Sao Paulo, Brazil

Took part in many projects, such as 'NFe', 'CTe', 'SPED Fiscal', and 'SPED Contribuições', for the Finantial Department. Responsible for the analysis, testing, and implementation. Some small application were also developed using VBA and C#.

American Express Senior Business Analyst May 2007 - October 2008 (1 year 6 months) Uberlândia, Minas Gerais, Brazil

Responsible for designing projects, leading a team of programmers during coding fase, testing, validating, and implementing in the client department.

## Education

University of Toronto
Full-Stack Web Development · (2020 - 2020)

Universidade Ibirapuera

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (1999 - 2003)